http://www.stanleylondon.com/privacy.htm

Menu
HomePersonalized CompassesDesk CompassesPocket CompassesWorking Compass JewelryNautical InstrumentsBrass SextantsBrass TelescopesBrass Ship's BellsBoatswain's PipesDecorDesk & Shelf ItemsStorage BoxesWeather Glass BarometersWall ItemsEngraved PlaquesPersonalized Aluminum Plaques EngravedPersonalized Brass Plaques EngravedPersonalized Commemorative Brass Bell Plaques EngravedPersonalized Outdoor UV Stable Plaques EngravedSpecialsAstronomical InstrumentsBrass Armillary SpheresAstrolabesCalculators & CalendarsNocturnalsCompassesDesk CompassesPocket CompassesSundial CompassesMeasuring InstrumentsAbney LevelsAdmiral Fitzroy Storm GlassesBrass Balance ScalesDumpy LevelsSailboat InclinometersSpirit LevelsTheodolitesMounted Presentation PlaquesAward PlaquesSextant PlaquesNautical Home DecorBarwareCake Serving SetCollapsible Drinking CupsStainless Steel FlasksThermal BottlesWine Corkscrew SetsMagnets & OrnamentsOffice DecorBusiness Card CasesDesk BellsWood GavelsOptical InstrumentsBinocularsEngravable Brass TelescopesDesk TelescopesFloor Standing TelescopesHandheld TelescopesMagnifiersDesk MagnifiersHandheld MagnifiersPersonal AccessoriesBookmarksCompact MirrorsJewelryAccessoriesNecklace ChainsJewelry BoxesCostume JewelryRhodium-Plated JewelryStainless Steel PendantsSterling Silver Compass Lockets and PendantsKey ChainsLuggage TagsMoney ClipsSewing KitsSmoking AccessoriesCigar CuttersCigar HoldersLightersTravel Clocks and WatchesWalking SticksSwords, Cutlasses & KnivesSwords and CutlassesBowie Knives & Damascus KnivesShip's InstrumentsBarometers and ClocksShip's BarometersShip's ClocksChart DividersDiver's HelmetsWooden Ship's WheelsShip's Telegraphs
Account
Home
Information Regarding Stanley London's Privacy Practices
Information Regarding Stanley London's Privacy Practices
This document describes Stanley London's (and its parent corporation, Castle Navigation Inc. here after referred to as Stanley London) policy regarding information received about you during visits to our web site. The amount and type of information received depends on how you use our site.
Normal Web Site Usage:You can visit Stanley London's web site to read product, company, and ordering information, or use our on-line tools (order tracking, etc.) without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. The only information we collect and store during normal web site usage is the name of your Internet service provider, the web site that referred you to us, the pages you request and the date and time of those requests. We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of customer visits. During normal web site usage we do not collect or store personally identifiable information such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number or social security number. Collection of personally identifiable information:When ordering products and services, Stanley London requests personally identifiable information. This information, such as name, phone numbers, shipping or mailing address, e-mail address, credit card account information, and possibly additional information, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data by Stanley London and is used to fulfill your request. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. The information you provide is used by Stanley London to improve the services we provide you. Your information is never provided to any other company for that company's independent use. A Cookie is a small file that a Web site transfers to your computer to allow it to remember specific information about your session while you are connected. Your computer will only share the information in the Cookie with the Web site that provided it, and no other Web site can request it. There are two types of Cookies, session and persistent. Session Cookies last only as long as your Web browser is open. Once you close your browser, the Cookie disappears. Persistent Cookies store information on your computer for longer periods of time. Our Shopping Cart uses Session Cookies to recognize your browser and to provide features such as temporary storage of items in your Shopping Cart. Persistent Cookies enable our systems to track information such as pageviews, traffic flow, search terms, and click through. We use this information to improve our sites and NEVER SHARE OR SELL this information. You can set your browser to warn you before accepting Cookies or to block Cookies. If you block Cookies, you will not be able to use our Shopping Cart. Electronic Mail sent to us that contains personal information:Internet users may decide to send Stanley London personally identifying information, for example, in a message containing information about your Stanley London order, product or requesting a service. Stanley London will only use this information to identify the user as a Stanley London customer and to determine how to respond to the electronic mail. We will not use this information other than to resolve the matter identified in the e-mail. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. A revised Privacy Policy will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date. Any revisions will be posted at least 10 days prior to its effective date. Copyright Notice:Copyright © 1998 - 2016 Stanley London. All rights reserved. All text, images, graphics, animation, videos, music, sounds and other materials on this site are subject to the copyrights and other intellectual property rights of Stanley London, its affiliated companies and its licensors. Stanley London owns the copyrights in the selection, coordination and arrangement of the materials on this site. These materials may not be copied for commercial use or distribution, nor may these materials be modified or reposted to other sites. Trademark Notice:Stanley London is a registered trademark of Castle Navigation Inc. All trademarks displayed on this site are subject to the U.S. trademark rights of Stanley London, or are used under agreement in the U.S. by Stanley London. The unauthorized use of any trademark displayed on this site is strictly prohibited.
Copyright © 2020 Stanley London, a division of Castle Navigation Inc. All rights reserved
Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy
